<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safar</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Safar</string>
    <string name="user_name_hint">username</string>
    <string name="password_hint">password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">confirm password</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up_button">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="dont_have_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_label">Log In</string>
    <string name="email_hint">email</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>
    <string name="visit_opt_itm">Visit Jordan</string>
    <string name="choose_a_country">Choose a country</string>
    <string name="visit">visit</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="favourite">Favourites</string>
    <string name="mark_as_favourite">Mark as favourite</string>
    <string name="admin_login_item">Admin Login</string>
    <string name="admin_login">Login</string>
    <string name="view_all_users">View All Users</string>
    <string name="long_click_on_user_note">*Click on a user to perform actions</string>
    <string name="enter_admin_password">Enter Admin Password</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="population">Population</string>
    <string name="area">Area</string>
    <string name="capital">Capital</string>
    <string name="neighbouring_countries">Neighbouring Countries</string>
    <string name="currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="quick_history">Quick History</string>

    <string name="jordan_quick_history">Jordan is a young state that occupies an ancient land,
        one that bears the traces of many civilizations. Separated from ancient Palestine by
        the Jordan River, the region played a prominent role in biblical history.\n\nThe ancient
        biblical kingdoms of Moab, Gilead, and Edom lie within its borders, as does the famed red
        stone city of Petra, the capital of the Nabatean kingdom and of the Roman province of
        Arabia Petraea. British traveler Gertrude Bell said of Petra, “It is like a fairy tale
        city, all pink and wonderful.” Part of the Ottoman Empire until 1918 and later a mandate
        of the United Kingdom, Jordan has been an independent kingdom since 1946.\n\nIt is among
        the most politically liberal countries of the Arab world, and, although it shares in the
        troubles affecting the region, its rulers have expressed a commitment to maintaining
        peace and stability.</string>

    <string name="japan_quick_history">Japan was settled about 35,000 years ago by Paleolithic
        people from the Asian mainland. At the end of the last Ice Age, about 10,000 years ago,
        a culture called the Jomon developed. Jomon hunter–gatherers fashioned fur clothing,
        wooden houses, and elaborate clay vessels. According to DNA analysis, the Ainu people
        may be descendants of the Jomon.\n\nThe second wave of settlement by the Yayoi people
        introduced metal–working, rice cultivation, and weaving to Japan. DNA evidence suggests
        that these settlers came from Korea.\n\nThe first era of recorded history in Japan is the
        Kofun (A.D. 250–538), which was characterized by large burial mounds or tumuli. The Kofun
        were headed by a class of aristocratic warlords; they adopted many Chinese customs
        and innovations.</string>

    <string name="canada_quick_history">The land that is now Canada was first home to nations of
        Indigenous peoples. In 1497 explorer John Cabot reached the east coast of present day
        Canada, and in 1534 Jacques Cartier explored the Gulf of St Lawrence and claimed the land
        for France.\n\nCartier established the first French settlement in 1541 at
        Charlesbourg-Royal, and by 1604 settlement of what is now known as New France begins.
        In 1627 The Company of One Hundred Associates is formed to help colonize New France.
        \n\nMeanwhile, Britain grants a Royal Charter in 1621 to Sir William Alexander giving him
        a barony that included Nova Scotia, Cape Breton Island, St John\'s Island (now Prince
        Edward Island), and the Gaspé Peninsula.</string>

    <string name="norway_quick_history">The earliest traces of human occupation in Norway are found
        along the coast, where the huge ice shelf of the last ice age first melted between 11,000
        and 8000 bce.\n\nThe oldest finds are stone tools dating from 9500 to 6000 bce, discovered
        in Finnmark in the north and Rogaland in the southwest. Theories of a “Komsa” type of
        stone-tool culture north of the Arctic Circle and a “Fosna” type from Trøndelag to Oslo
        Fjord were rendered obsolete in the 1970s. More recent finds along the entire coast
        revealed to archaeologists that the difference between the two can simply be ascribed to
        different types of tools and not to different cultures.\n\nCoastal fauna provided a means
        of livelihood for fishermen and hunters, who may have made their way along the southern
        coast about 10,000 bce when the interior was still covered with ice. It is now thought
        that these so-called “Arctic” peoples came from the south and followed the coast northward
        considerably later. Some may have come along the ice-free coast of the Kola Peninsula, but
        the evidence of this is still poor.</string>

    <string name="chile_quick_history">Before being discovered by the Europeans, Chile was inhabited
        by several tribes of Native Americans; including the Inca in the north and the Araucanian
        tribes in the south.In 1520 Ferdinand Magellan was the first European to see Chile. In 1540
        Pedro de Valdivia a Spanish conquistador came to Chile were he founded several cities,
        despite resistance from the Araucanians.\n\nOne of these cities he founded was Santiago,
        which is now Chile\'s capitol and largest city. In 1553 the Native Americans led several
        successful revolts against the Spanish conquerors, killing Valdivia and devastating most
        of the cities he founded. This lead to nearly 100 years of warfare. Eventually the Spanish
        dominated, but even then strife and conflicts continued for many more years.</string>

    <string name="uae_quick_history">The largest of these emirates, Abu Dhabi, which comprises more
        than three-fourths of the federation\’s total land area, is the centre of its oil industry
        and borders Saudi Arabia on the federation\’s southern and eastern borders. The port city of
        Dubai, located at the base of the mountainous Musandam Peninsula, is the capital of the
        emirate of Dubai and is one of the region\’s most vital commercial and financial centres,
        housing hundreds of multinational corporations in a forest of skyscrapers.\n\nThe smaller
        emirates of Sharjah, Umm al-Qaywayn, and Ra\ʾs Al-Khaymah also occupy the peninsula, whose
        protrusion north toward Iran forms the Strait of Hormuz linking the Persian Gulf to the Gulf
        of Oman. The federation\’s seventh member, Al-Fujayrah, faces the Gulf of Oman and is the
        only member of the union with no frontage along the Persian Gulf.</string>

    <string name="germany_quick_history">Germany, officially Federal Republic of Germany, German
        Deutschland or Bundesrepublik Deutschland, country of north-central Europe, traversing the
        continent\’s main physical divisions, from the outer ranges of the Alps northward across the
        varied landscape of the Central German Uplands and then across the North German Plain.
        \n\nOne of Europe\’s largest countries, Germany encompasses a wide variety of landscapes:
        the tall, sheer mountains of the south; the sandy, rolling plains of the north; the forested
        hills of the urbanized west; and the plains of the agricultural east.\n\nAt the spiritual
        heart of the country is the magnificent east-central city of Berlin, which rose phoenixlike
        from the ashes of World War II and now, after decades of partition, is the capital of a
        reunified Germany, and the Rhine River, which flows northward from Switzerland and is
        celebrated in visual art, literature, folklore, and song. </string>

    <string name="find_location">Find Location</string>
    <string name="find_public_places">Find Public Places</string>
    <string name="more_info">More Info</string>

    <string name="petra_more_info">PETRA … More Than A Wonder\n\nThe city of Petra, capital
        of the Nabataean Arabs, is one of the most famous archaeological sites in the world,
        it is Located 240 km south of the capital Amman and 120 km north of the red sea town of
        Aqaba, Petra the world wonder, is undoubtedly Jordan\'s most valuable
        treasure and greatest tourist attraction, and it is visited by tourists from all over
        the world.</string>

    <string name="wadi_rum_more_info">Wadi Rum has been inhabited by many human cultures since
        prehistoric times, with many cultures–including the Nabataeans–leaving their mark in the
        form of petroglyphs, inscriptions, and temple. In the West, Wadi Rum may be best known for
        its connection with British officer T. E. Lawrence, who passed through several times
        during the Arab Revolt of 1917–18. In the 1980s one of the rock formations in Wadi Rum,
        originally known as Jabal al-Mazmar (The Mountain of (the) Plague), was named \"The Seven
        Pillars of Wisdom,\" after Lawrence\'s book penned in the aftermath of the war, though the
        \'Seven Pillars\' referred to in the book have no connection with Rum.</string>

    <string name="aqaba_more_info">Aqaba\'s strategic location at the northeastern tip of the Red
        Sea between the continents of Asia and Africa, has made its port important over the course
        of thousands of years.\n\nThe ancient city was called Elath, adopted in Latin as Aela and in
        Arabic as Ayla. Its strategic location and proximity to copper mines made it a regional
        hub for copper production and trade in the Chalcolithic period. Aela became a bishopric
        under Byzantine rule and later became a Latin Catholic titular see after Islamic conquest
        around AD 650, when it became known as Ayla; the name Aqaba is late medieval. The Great
        Arab Revolt\'s Battle of Aqaba, depicted in the film Lawrence of Arabia,resulted in victory
        for Arab forces over the Ottoman defenders.</string>

    <string name="roman_theater_more_info">The Roman Amphitheater is located in the eastern part
        of the Jordanian capital, Amman. It is specifically at the foot of Jabal Al-Joufah, on a
        hill opposite the Amman Citadel. A Greek inscription on one of the pillars indicates that
        this amphitheater was built in honour of Emperor Antonius Pius (138–161 CE).\n\nThe large and
        steeply raked structure could seat about 6,000 people: built into the hillside, it was
        oriented north to keep the sun off the spectators.\n\nIt was divided into three horizontal
        sections (diazomata). Side entrances (paradoi) existed at ground level, one leading to the
        orchestra and the other to the stage. Rooms behind these entrances now house the Jordan
        Museum of Popular Tradition on the one side, and the Jordan Folklore Museum on the other
        side.</string>

    <string name="nebo_more_info">During the 4th century AD a church was constructed on Mount Nebo,
        and said to honor Moses, although the church was most likely built on the site of a much
        older building of worship.\n\nOver the next two hundred years the church was extended and
        improved to cater for the larger influx of pilgrims as the word of Christianity spread
        across the world. Finally, the church became part of a monastery and was increased in
        size to become a basilica and became the focus point of pilgrimage for over six hundred
        years.</string>

    <string name="imperial_more_info">The Tokyo Imperial Palace \'Imperial Residence\' is the usual
        residence of the Emperor of Japan. It is a large park-like area located in the Chiyoda
        district of the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo and contains several buildings including the main
        palace, some residences of the Imperial Family, an archive, museums and administrative
        offices.\n\nIt is built on the site of the old Edo Castle. The total area including the
        gardens is 1.15 square kilometres (0.44 sq mi). During the height of the 1980s Japanese
        property bubble, the palace grounds were valued by some to be more than the value of all
        of the real estate in the state of California.</string>

    <string name="shrine_more_info">Itsukushima Shrine is a Shinto shrine on the island of
        Itsukushima (popularly known as Miyajima), best known for its "floating" torii gate.
        It is in the city of Hatsukaichi in Hiroshima Prefecture in Japan. The shrine complex
        is listed as a UNESCO World Heritage Site, and the Japanese government has designated
        several buildings and possessions as National Treasures.\n\nThe Itsukushima shrine is
        one of Japan\'s most popular tourist attractions. It is most famous for its dramatic gate,
        or torii on the outskirts of the shrine, the sacred peaks of Mount Misen, extensive forests,
        and its aesthetic ocean view. The shrine complex itself consists of two main buildings:
        the Honsha shrine and the Sessha Marodo-jinja, as well as 17 other different buildings
        and structures that help to distinguish it. The complex is also listed as a UNESCO World
        Heritage Site, and six of its buildings and possessions have been designated by the Japanese
        government as National Treasures.</string>

    <string name="fuji_more_info">Mount Fuji located on the island of Honshū, is the highest
        mountain in Japan, standing 3,776.24 m (12,389.2 ft). It is the second-highest volcano
        located on an island in Asia (after Mount Kerinci on the island of Sumatra), and
        seventh-highest peak of an island on Earth. Mount Fuji is an active stratovolcano that
        last erupted from 1707 to 1708. The mountain stands about 100 km (62 mi) southwest of
        Tokyo and is visible from there on clear days. Mount Fuji\'s exceptionally symmetrical
        cone, which is snow-capped for about five months of the year, is commonly used as a
        cultural icon of Japan and it is frequently depicted in art and photography, as well
        as visited by sightseers and climbers.</string>

    <string name="arashiyama_more_info">Arashiyama is in the far west of Kyoto, tucked along the
        base of the Arashiyama Mountains (meaning \"Storm Mountains\”). It\’s a fair distance from
        the center of Kyoto: whether you go by train, bus, bicycle or taxi, you\’re generally
        looking at about a 30-minute trip. Still, it\’s worth it for the number of great
        sights here.</string>

    <string name="osaka_castle_more_info">The main tower of Osaka Castle is situated on a plot of
        land roughly one square kilometer. It is built on two raised platforms of landfill
        supported by sheer walls of cut rock, using a technique called Burdock piling, each
        overlooking a moat. The central castle building is five stories on the outside and eight
        stories on the inside, and built atop a tall stone foundation to protect its occupants
        from attackers.\n\nThe castle grounds, which cover approximately 61,000 square meters
        (15 acres), contain thirteen structures that have been designated as important cultural
        assets by the Japanese government.</string>

    <string name="bay_of_fundy_more_info">The Bay of Fundy is a bay
        between the Canadian provinces of New Brunswick and Nova Scotia, with a small portion
        touching the US state of Maine. It has an extremely high tidal range. The name is likely
        a corruption of the French word Fendu, meaning \"split\".</string>

    <string name="quebec_more_info">Old Quebec is a historic neighbourhood of Quebec City, Quebec,
        Canada. Comprising the Upper Town and LowerTown, the area is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
        Administratively,Old Quebec is part of the Vieux-Québec–Cap-Blanc–colline Parlementaire
        district in the borough of La Cité-Limoilou.\n\nThe area is commonly referred to as
        \"the Old City\" or \"Quebec\'s Old City\" in English. It is sometimes referred to as the
        Latin Quarter (French: Quartier latin) as well, although this title refers more to area
        around the Séminaire de Québec, the original site of Laval University.</string>

    <string name="stanley_park_more_info">Stanley Park is a 405-hectare (1,001-acre) public park
        that borders the downtown of Vancouver in British Columbia, Canada, and is mostly
        surrounded by waters of Burrard Inlet and English Bay.\n\nThe park has a long history
        and was one of the first areas to be explored in the city. The land was originally used
        by Indigenous peoples for thousands of years before British Columbia was colonized by the
        British during the 1858 Fraser Canyon Gold Rush. For many years after colonization, the
        future park with its abundant resources would also be home to non-Indigenous settlers.
        The land was later turned into Vancouver\'s first park when the city incorporated in 1886.
        It was named after Lord Stanley, 16th Earl of Derby, a British politician who had recently
        been appointed Governor General. It was originally known as Coal Peninsula and was set
        aside for military fortifications to guard the entrance to Vancouver harbour. In 1886
        Vancouver city council successfully sought a lease of the park which was granted for $1
        per year. In September 1888 Lord Stanley opened the park in his name.</string>

    <string name="butchart_more_info">The Butchart Gardens is a group of floral display gardens
        in Brentwood Bay, British Columbia, Canada, located near Victoria on Vancouver Island.
        The gardens receive over a million visitors each year. The gardens have been designated
        a National Historic Site of Canada.</string>

    <string name="banff_national_park_more_info">Banff National Park  is Canada\'s oldest national
        park, established in 1885. Located in Alberta\'s Rocky Mountains, 110–180 kilometres
         (68–112 mi) west of Calgary, Banff encompasses 6,641 square kilometres(2,564 sq mi)
        of mountainous terrain, with many glaciers and ice fields, dense coniferous forest,
        and alpine landscapes. The Infields Parkway extends from Lake Louise, connecting
        to Jasper National Park in the north. Provincial forests and Yoho National Park are
        neighbours to the west, while Kootenay National Park is located to the south and Kananask is
        Country to the southeast. The main commercial centre of the park is the town of Banff, in
        the Bow River valley.</string>

    <string name="bryggen_more_info">Bryggen (the dock), also known as Tyskebryggen, is a series
        of Hanseatic heritage commercial buildings lining up the eastern side of the Vågen harbour
        in the city of Bergen, Norway. Bryggen has been on the UNESCO list for World Cultural
        Heritage sites since 1979.\n\nThe city of Bergen was founded around 1070 within the
        boundaries of Tyskebryggen. Around 1350 a Kontor of the Hanseatic League was established
        there, and Tyskebryggen became the centre of the Hanseatic commercial activities in Norway.
        Today, Bryggen houses museums, shops, restaurants and pubs. </string>

    <string name="preikestolen_more_info">Preikestolen or Prekestolen (English: \"The Pulpit Rock\",
        "Pulpit", or "Preacher’s Chair") is a tourist attraction in the municipality of Strand in
        Rogaland county, Norway. Preikestolen is a steep cliff which rises 604 metres (1,982 ft)
        above Lysefjorden. Atop the cliff, there is an almost flat top of approximately 25 by 25
        metres (82 ft × 82 ft). Preikestolen is located near the Western part of the fjord, and on
        its North side.\n\nTourism at the site has been increasing in the early 21st century,
        with between 150,000 and 200,000 visitors in 2012, making it one of the most visited
        natural tourist attractions in Norway. BASE jumpers often leap from the cliff. Due to its
        increased popularity, there is currently a project under way to improve the most used path
        to the site - a 3.8-kilometre (2.4 mi) long hike. </string>

    <string name="lofoten_more_info">Lofoten is an archipelago and a traditional district in the
        county of Nordland, Norway. Lofoten is known for a distinctive scenery with dramatic
        mountains and peaks, open sea and sheltered bays, beaches and untouched lands. Its largest
        town, Leknes, is approximately 169 km (105 mi) inside the Arctic Circle and approximately
        2,420 km (1,500 mi) away from the North Pole, making Lofoten one of the world\'s northernmost
        populated regions. Though lying within the Arctic Circle, the archipelago experiences one
        of the world\'s largest elevated temperature anomalies relative to its high latitude.</string>

    <string name="geiranger_fjord_more_info">The Geiranger Fjord is a fjord in the Sunnmøre
        region of Møre og Romsdal county, Norway. It is located entirely in the Stranda Municipality.
        It is a 15-kilometre (9.3 mi) -long branch off the Sunnylvsfjorden, which is a branch off
        the Storfjorden (Great Fjord). The small village of Geiranger is located at the end of the
        fjord where the Geirangelva river empties into it. </string>

    <string name="akershus_fortress_more_info">Akershus Fortress or Akershus Castle is a medieval
        castle in the Norwegian capital Oslo that was built to protect and provide a royal residence
        for the city. Since the Middle Ages the fortress has been the namesake and centre of the
        main fief and later main county of Akershus, which was originally one of Norway\'s four
        main regions and which included most of Eastern Norway. The fortress itself was located
        within the Akershus main county until 1919, and also within the smaller Akershus sub county
        until 1842.\n\nThe castle has also been used as a military base, a prison and is currently
        the temporary office of the Prime minister of Norway.</string>

    <string name="anakena_more_info">Anakena is a white coral sand beach in Rapa Nui National Park
        on Rapa Nui (Easter Island), a Chilean island in the Pacific Ocean. Anakena has two ahus;
        Ahu-Ature has a single moai and Ahu Nao-Nao has seven, two of which have deteriorated.
        It also has a palm grove and a car park.\n\nAnakena is unusual for Easter Island in that it
        is one of only two small sandy beaches in an otherwise rocky coastline. </string>

    <string name="el_tatio_more_info">El Tatio is a geyser field located in the Andes Mountains
        of northern Chile at 4,320 metres (14,170 ft) above mean sea level. Various etymologies
        have been proposed for the name \"El Tatio\", which might mean \"oven\" or \"grandfather\".
        It is the third-largest geyser field in the world and the largest in the Southern
        Hemisphere.\n\nEl Tatio lies at the western foot of a series of stratovolcanoes, which
        run along the border between Chile and Bolivia. This series of volcanoes is part of the
        Central Volcanic Zone, one of several volcanic belts in the Andes, and there are no
        recorded historical eruptions at the Tatio volcanoes. El Tatio is also part of the
        Altiplano–Puna volcanic complex (APVC), a system of large calderas and associated
        ignimbrites, which have been the sources of supereruptions. Some of these calderas may
        be the source of heat for the El Tatio geothermal system. </string>

    <string name="cape_horn_more_info">Cape Horn is the southernmost headland of the Tierra del Fuego
        archipelago of southern Chile, and is located on the small Hornos Island. Although not
        the most southerly point of South America (which are the Diego Ramírez Islands), Cape
        Horn marks the northern boundary of the Drake Passage and marks where the Atlantic and
        Pacific Oceans meet.\n\nCape Horn is the southernmost headland of the Tierra del Fuego
        archipelago of southern Chile, and is located on the small Hornos Island. It marks both
        the northern boundary of the Drake Passage and where the Atlantic and Pacific Oceans
        meet.</string>

    <string name="villarrica_more_info">Villarrica is a city and commune in southern Chile located
        on the western shore of Villarrica Lake in the Province of Cautín, Araucanía Region 746
        km (464 mi) south of Santiago and close to the Villarrica Volcano ski center to the south
        east. Residents of Villarrica are known as Villarriquences.\n\nTourism, grain and dairy
        farming, and forestry are the main economic activities of the community. The climate is
        mild and humid with the greatest rainfall experienced between May and July
        (autumn and winter). The dry season is between December and February (Summer).\n\nOther
        lakes found nearby include Calafquén, Caburgua, Huilipilún and Colico. In the summer water
        sports and sunbathing are popular activities in the warm temperatures experienced at the
        low altitudes ranging from 200 to 500m above sea level.</string>

    <string name="valley_of_the_moon_more_info">Valley of the Moon is located 13 kilometres (8 mi)
        west of San Pedro de Atacama, to the north of Chile in the Cordillera de la Sal, in the
        Atacama desert. It has various stone and sand formations which have been carved by wind
        and water. It has an impressive range of color and texture, looking somewhat similar to
        the surface of the moon. There are also dry lakes where the composition of salt makes a
        white covering layer of the area. It presents diverse saline outcrops which appear
        like man-made sculptures. There are also a great variety of caverns.\n\nWhen the sun sinks
        it defines the landscape while the wind blows among the rocks and the sky passes from pink
        color to purple and finally black. Valle de la Luna is a part of the Reserve National los
        Flamencos and was declared a Nature Sanctuary in 1982 for its natural environment and
        strange lunar landscape, from which its name is derived. The Atacama desert is also
        considered one of the driest places on earth, as some areas have not received a single
        drop of rain in hundreds of years. A prototype for a Mars rover was tested there by
        scientists because of the valley\'s dry and forbidding terrains.</string>

    <string name="burj_khalifa_more_info">The Burj Khalifa known as the Burj Dubai prior to its
        inauguration in 2010, is a skyscraper in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. With a total height
        of 829.8 m (2,722 ft, just over half a mile) and a roof height (excluding antenna,
        but including a 244 m) of 828 m (2,717 ft), the Burj Khalifa has been the tallest
        structure and building in the world since its topping out in 2009 (preceded by Taipei 101).
    </string>

    <string name="dubai_aquarium_more_info">Dubai Aquarium and Underwater Zoo is home to thousands of
    aquatic animals, comprising over 140 species. Over 400 Sharks and Rays live in our 10 million
    litre tank, including Sand Tiger Sharks, Giant Groupers, and a host of other marine species.
    A series of carefully designed experiences will allow our visitors to come face to face with
    our aquatic residents for memorable moments with friends and family.</string>

    <string name="palm_jumeirah_more_info">Palm Jumeirah, artificial offshore islands in Dubai,
        United Arab Emirates, the site of private residences and hotels. From the air, the
        archipelago resembles a stylized palm tree within a circle. Palm Jumeirah was built in
        the early 21st century and was largely financed from Dubai\’s substantial income from
        petroleum.</string>

    <string name="dubai_frame_more_info">The Dubai Frame is located next to the star gate in
        Zabeel Park. The structure is a colossal rectangular picture frame, with two towers of
        93 meters wide and 152 meters height straddling an enormous 100 square meter bridge that
        forms the top of the picture frame.</string>

    <string name="burj_al_arab_more_info">It\’s exceptionally tall Burj Al Arab Jumeirah –
        which stands at 321m – is 14m taller than the Eiffel Tower and only 60m shorter than
        the Empire State building. </string>

    <string name="brandenburg_gate_more_info">The Brandenburg Gate is one of Berlin\’s most renowned
        landmarks. Over the last 200 plus years it has endured several wars, invasions, and intense
        political changes. Since its construction, the Gate has connected Berlin to the world, and
        today it stands as a symbol of peace and unity.</string>

    <string name="the_rhine_valley_more_info">The Middle Rhine was the heart of the medieval Holy
        Roman Empire and the region was a magnet for great artistry, ingenuity, and craftsmanship.
        During its heyday, it was one of the most important trading areas in Europe—arguably, the
        world. Journey through the Romantic Rhine Valley and discover the culture, the stories, the
        gastronomy and wine that makes this one of Europe’s most renowned romantic landscapes.</string>

    <string name="neuschwanstein_castle_more_info">The castle was intended as a home for the King,
        until he died in 1886. It was open to the public shortly after his death. Since then more
        than 61 million people have visited Neuschwanstein Castle. More than 1.3 million people visit
        annually, with as many as 6,000 per day in the summer.</string>

    <string name="museum_island_more_info">The Museum Island is a museum complex on the northern
        part of the Spree Island in the historic heart of Berlin. It is one of the most visited
        sights of Germany\'s capital and one of the most important museum sites in Europe.</string>

    <string name="rothenburg_ob_der_tauber_more_info">It\'s a town in the district of Ansbach of
        Mittelfranken (Middle Franconia), the Franconia region of Bavaria, Germany. It is well known
        for its well-preserved medieval old town, a destination for tourists from around the world.
        It is part of the popular Romantic Road through southern Germany.</string>

    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="custom_search">CUSTOM SEARCH</string>
    <string name="find">Find</string>
    <string name="gyms">Gyms</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee Shops</string>
    <string name="Parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="hair_salon">Hair Salons</string>
    <string name="search">search</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="about">About Jordan</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="enter_new_email">enter new email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="enter_new_username">enter new username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">new password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_text_view">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="add_user">Add User</string>
    <string name="search_item">Search</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="jordan_culture_1">The culture of Jordan is based in Arabic and Islamic elements.
        Jordan stands at the intersection of the three continents of the ancient world, lending it
        geographic and population diversity. Notable aspects of the culture include traditional
        music and clothing of Jordan, and interest in sports. These include football and basketball
        as well as other imported sports, mainly from western Europe and the United States.</string>

    <string name="jordan_culture_2">More than 40% of the population lives in the metropolis of
        Amman, concentrating the culture of Jordan in that city. Jordanian pop culture is heavily
        influenced by the West. European and American music, movies, fashion and other forms of
        entertainment are popular among Jordan\'s people. Clubbing and partying culture are present
        in Amman, especially in the Western half of the city. A small minority of youth, mostly
        the richin West Amman. Amman is consistently declared one of the most westernised and
        modern cities in the region. Malls, Western-brand stores, and hotels are important elements
        in Amman\'s urban life, especially in the Western side.</string>

    <string name="japan_culture_1">Ishin-denshin is a Japanese idiom which denotes a form of
        interpersonal communication through unspoken mutual understanding. Isagiyosa is a virtue
        of the capability of accepting death with composure. Cherry blossoms are a symbol of
        isagiyosa in the sense of embracing the transience of the world. Hansei is a central
        idea in Japanese culture, meaning to acknowledge one\'s own mistake and to pledge
        improvement. Kotodama refers to the Japanese belief that mystical powers dwell in
        words and names.</string>

    <string name="japan_culture_2">Officially, Japan has 16 national, government-recognized
        holidays. Public holidays in Japan are regulated by the Public Holiday Law (Kokumin no
        Shukujitsu ni Kansuru Hōritsu) of 1948. Beginning in 2000, Japan implemented the Happy
        Monday System, which moved a number of national holidays to Monday in order to obtain a
        long weekend. The national holidays in Japan are New Year\'s Day on January 1, Coming of
        Age Day on the second Monday of January, National Foundation Day on February 11, The
        Emperor\'s Birthday on February 23, Vernal Equinox Day on March 20 or 21, Shōwa Day on
        April 29, Constitution Memorial Day on May 3, Greenery Day on May 4, Children\'s Day on
        May 5, Marine Day on the third Monday of July, Mountain Day on August 11, Respect for the
        Aged Day on the third Monday of September, Autumnal Equinox on September 23 or 24, Health
        and Sports Day on the second Monday of October, Culture Day on November 3, and Labor
        Thanksgiving Day on November 23.</string>

    <string name="canada_culture_1">Canadian literature is often divided into French- and
        English-language literatures, which are rooted in the literary traditions of France and
        Britain, respectively.[401] There are four major themes that can be found within historical
        Canadian literature; nature, frontier life, Canada\'s position within the world, all three
        of which tie into the garrison mentality. By the 1990s, Canadian literature was viewed as
        some of the world\'s best. Canada\'s ethnic and cultural diversity are reflected in its
        literature, with many of its most prominent modern writers focusing on ethnic life.
        Arguably, the best-known living Canadian writer internationally (especially since the
        deaths of Robertson Davies and Mordecai Richler) is Margaret Atwood, a prolific novelist,
        poet, and literary critic.</string>

    <string name="canada_culture_2">Numerous other Canadian authors have accumulated international
        literary awards, including Nobel Laureate Alice Munro, who has been called the best living
        writer of short stories in English; and Booker Prize recipient Michael Ondaatje, who is
        perhaps best known for the novel The English Patient, which was adapted as a film of the
        same name that won the Academy Award for Best Picture.</string>

    <string name="norway_culture_1">Norway\'s culinary traditions show the influence of long
        seafaring and farming traditions, with salmon (fresh and cured), herring (pickled or
        marinated), trout, codfish, and other seafood, balanced by cheeses (such as brunost),
        dairy products, and breads.</string>

    <string name="norway_culture_2">Lefse is a Norwegian potato flatbread, usually topped with
        large amounts of butter and sugar, most common around Christmas. Some traditional Norwegian
        dishes include lutefisk, smalahove and raspeball. Some quirky Norwegian speciality is
        rakefisk, which is a fermented trout, consumed with thin flatbread (flatbrød, not lefse)
        and sour cream. And the most popular pastry among all population is vaffel. It is different
        from Belgian in taste and consistency and is served with sour cream, brown cheese, butter
        and sugar, or strawberry or raspberry jam, which can all be mixed or eaten separately.</string>

    <string name="chile_culture_1">From the period between early agricultural settlements and
        up to the late pre-Hispanic period, northern Chile was a region of Andean culture that
        was influenced by altiplano traditions spreading to the coastal valleys of the north,
        while southern regions were areas of Mapuche cultural activities. Throughout the colonial
        period following the conquest, and during the early Republican period, the country\'s
        culture was dominated by the Spanish.</string>

    <string name="chile_culture_2">Other European influences, primarily English, French, and
        German began in the 19th century and have continued to this day. German migrants influenced
        the Bavarian style rural architecture and cuisine in the south of Chile in cities such as
        Valdivia, Frutillar, Puerto Varas, Osorno, Temuco, Puerto Octay, Llanquihue, Faja Maisan,
        Victoria and Puerto Montt.</string>

    <string name="uae_culture_1">The United Arab Emirates (UAE) has a diverse society.
        The country\'s historical population as a small tribal community that has changed with
        the arrival of other nationals, in the mid-20th century. The country was also part of the
        British Empire until 1971. Emirati culture is based on Arabian culture, with influences
        from the cultures of East Africa and Indian Subcontinent. The religion of Islam has had a
        prominent influence on local architecture, music, attire, cuisine, and lifestyle.</string>


    <string name="uae_culture_2">Five times every day, Muslims are called to prayer from the
        minarets of mosques, which are scattered around the country. The weekend begins on Friday
        due to Friday being the holiest day for Muslims; most Muslim countries have a
        Friday-Saturday or Thursday-Friday weekend. The city of Al Ain in Abu Dhabi is a
        UNESCO World Heritage site. The Emirate of Sharjah was named \"The Cultural capital
        of the Arab World\" by UNESCO in 1998 and the \"Capital of Islamic Culture for 2014\"
        by the OIC.</string>

    <string name="germany_culture_1">The birthplace of the modern printing press and of influential
        schools of philosophy and artistic styles, Germany has long played an important role in
        Western culture, and the arts have been central to Germany\’s idea of itself. Indeed,
        the historian Hagen Schulze observed that.</string>

    <string name="germany_culture_2">That ideal fell only when the German nation began to experiment
        with power and expand militarily, but it remains fondly held by contemporary German
        intellectuals as a model worthy of emulation in a new Europe. During the period of partition,
        West Germany, as heir to Germany\’s older regions, was custodian of the greater portion of
        the country\’s rich cultural legacy.</string>

    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="change_password">CHANGE PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="delete_all_users">DELETE ALL USERS</string>
    <string name="usernameInProfile">Username:</string>
    <string name="userEmailInProfile">Email:</string>
    <string name="profile_activity_tip">*Click on an item to change.</string>
    <string name="current_password">current password</string>
    <string name="see_wikipedia">See Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
    <string name="favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="add_to_favourites">Add To Favourites</string>
    <string name="empty_fav_countries">No Favourite Countries Yet</string>
    <string name="empty_fav_attractions">No Favourite Attractions Yet</string>
    <string name="clear_favourite_countries">Clear Favourite Countries</string>
    <string name="clear_favourite_attractions">Clear Favourite Attractions</string>
    <string name="sign_in_automatically">Sign In Automatically</string>
    <string name="remove_from_favourites">Remove From Favourites</string>
    <string name="see_details">See Details</string>
    <string name="no_registered_users_yet">No Registered Users Yet</string>
    <string name="go_to_favourites">Go To Favourites</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="rate_safar">Rate Safar</string>

</resources>






















